6zap.com 2012-06-06

# Funambol: Privacy Policy

## Funambol is committed to protecting the privacy of site visitors, prospects and customers. We will not sell your personal information to anyone. The information you provide on an online form will be processed by Funambol and its service providers within the United States.

The purpose of this policy is to explain the types of information we obtain from people via the Funambol web site, how the information is obtained, how it is used, how it may be obtained by others, and how its use and disclosure can be restricted. Funambol's website is governed by the following privacy principles:

### Principle 1: General Data Collection

Our site automatically gathers certain anonymous traffic information, such as Internet protocol addresses and other numeric codes used to identify a computer. This information is aggregated and does not personally identify you, but it helps us improve the site and the services we offer. For example, we may use IP addresses to monitor site usage to better prepare for anticipated traffic patterns. We may also gather user information that we save on your computer (not on our server) as “cookies” in order to streamline the site experience.

### Principle 2: Information Requests

Funambol requests personal information from you in order to gather your contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, email address, and zip code. Some of this information is optional and you may choose not to provide it. Funambol may use the information to contact you to further discuss your interest in our company and products, to send information regarding product updates, and to send a newsletter. You can opt out of being further contacted by us, or receiving such further information from us by emailing info@funambol.com with a subject of unsubscribe. Except as stated in this policy or as provided in the Funambol license and services agreement, we do not disclose your personal information to any third party, with the exception that we may disclose your information to one of our distribution partners who can meet your needs. Funambol reserves the right to maintain information on customers who have violated our license and services agreement.

### Principle 3: Disclosure

Funambol will not sell your individual Information to any third parties. Funambol does not disclose your personal Information to third parties, except as set forth in this policy and in cases where Funambol, acting in good faith, believes that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with a legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order; or (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Funambol; (3) enforce the license and services agreement.

### Principle 4: Solicitation

By registering at this site, you are authorizing Funambol to email you requested documents, a periodic newsletter, and occasional invitations to attend Funambol partner activities. Funambol will not send you any unsolicited information, including email, if at any time you decide to opt-out of receiving such information by clicking here. However, under certain circumstances, Funambol may be required to send customers updated information about our products.

### Frequently Asked Privacy Questions

##### What are cookies?

Cookies are files of information that a web site stores on your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. Cookies allow web sites to "remember" users across pages of a site and across multiple visits to a site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features to their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. Cookies cannot damage user files, nor can they read unrelated information from a user's hard drive. If you would prefer, you can set your settings to refuse cookies.

##### Is my personal information secure?

The personal information collected by Funambol is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the general public. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, while we strive to protect your personal information, Funambol cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

### Appendix

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to webmaster@funambol.com.

Last updated: 24 October 2007
